Guide to the New-York Historical Society Building Renovations and Maintenance Records 1938-2017 NYHS-RG 4
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. 1990s Capital Improvement Projects, circa 1984-2001 (bulk 1989-2000); 16.38 Linear feet in 26 document boxes and two drawers of oversize folders
  - Subseries II.A. Initial Planning & Projects, circa 1984-1994 (bulk, 1989-1993); 5.02 Linear feet
    The series is arranged in two sets. The first is in rough chronological order and by topic. The second set consists of "additional files" found after the first set of documents was processed; this second set is appended to the container list in alphabetical order by subject.
    The material was originally found in three record cartons and appeared to have been previously compiled from a few N-YHS departments or offices. The processing archivist re-arranged the folders to bring like matter together, but left the contents of each folder to remain as found, even where there was overlap in subjects or documents. Documents were re-housed to archival folders; the labels in the container list were transcribed from the original labels. Label titles created or modified by the processing archivist are those in [brackets].
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (1 of 4 folders), 1989 May-September (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (2 of 4 folders), 1989 September-October (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (3 of 4 folders), 1989 November-December (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (4 of 4 folders). Oversize, 1989 September-October (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 7)
      Includes blueline copies of the preliminary schedule for roof and facade repairs and schedule as of October 23, 1989, with the project plan ranging from October 1989 to October 1991. Also includes plans for renovations of the toilet rooms and entry area (September-October 1989).
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect. Minutes & Agendas, 1989 July-1990 July (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (1 of 3 folders), 1990 January (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (2 of 3 folders), 1990 January (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect (3 of 3 folders), 1990 March-August (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect. Project & Maintenance Manuals, 1990 September (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
      Includes the Maintenance Manual for Roof and Facade Renovation (masonry portion prepared by Facade Maintenance Design) and the Project Manual for Roof Repairs (H.B. Fishman & Co.).
    - Allan Greenberg, Architect. Interim Status Report, 1990 September-October (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - BKD [Barbara Knowles Debs]. Allan Greenberg, Architect., 1989 April-1991 January (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
    - BKD [Barbara Knowles Debs] Notes, 1990 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
    - Capital Projects Bills & Notes, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
    - [Certificate of No Effect], 1989 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
    - Air Quality & Environmental Control Survey, 1989 November-December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. Initial Roof Survey, 1989 May, August (Offsite-box 3, Folder 6)
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. Roof Repair Plan, 1989 [August?] (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 8)
      Includes drawing # R-5.
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. (1 of 4 folders), 1989 May-December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 7)
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. (2 of 4 folders), 1990 August-1991 June (Offsite-box 3, Folder 8)
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. (3 of 4 folders), 1992 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 9)
    - H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc. (4 of 4 folders), 1993 January-February (Offsite-box 3, Folder 10)
    - Temporary Roof Repairs, 1989 October, 1990 July (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - Renovations. Roof Bids, 1990 November-December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
    - Roof Repair Permit, 1990 December (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
    - Renovations Contracts. Roof, 1990 June-1991 May (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
    - Roof Renovations. Minutes, 1991 February-March (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
    - William Higgins & Company, Inc., 1989 September-1991 January (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
    - [Facade Rehabilitation Proposal], 1989 July 7 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    - Facade Assessment Report [Facade Maintenance Design], 1989 September (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
      Report dated September 18, 1989, for the 15 West 76th Street townhouse, includes color images. Also includes a report dated September 19, 1989, from Severud Associates concerning their structural review of the townhouse.
    - Facade Maintenance Design. Drawings, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 9)
      Includes two blueline plans by Facade Maintenance Design: 76th Street wall elevations and details (drawings #A1 and A2); stamped by the Department of Buildings on June 18, 1990.
    - Shiffer, Litchfield Associates Architects [Facade Maintenance Design] (1 of 2 folders), 1989 December-1991 March (Offsite-box 3, Folder 19)
      An oversize blueline of plans for masonry repairs was moved to the following folder.
    - Shiffer, Litchfield Associates Architects [Facade Maintenance Design] (2 of 2 folders). Oversize, 1991 March 8 (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 10)
      Includes an oversize blueline for masonry repairs (sheet #A-1), marked as approved by the Landmarks Preservation Commission on April 8, 1991.
    - Arco Consultants, Inc. (1 of 2), 1990 June-1991 March (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
      Two oversize blueline plans were moved to the following folder.
    - Arco Consultants, Inc. (2 of 2). Oversize, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 11)
      Includes two oversize blueline plans by Facade Maintenance Design: 76th Street wall elevations and details (drawings #A1 and A2); stamped by the Department of Buildings on June 18, 1990.
    - Renovations Contracts. Luman Reed Gallery (1 of 4 folders), 1990 May-August (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
    - Renovations Contracts. Luman Reed Gallery (2 of 4 folders), 1990 August (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
    - Renovations Contracts. Luman Reed Gallery (3 of 4 folders), 1990 September (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
    - Renovations Contracts. Luman Reed Gallery (4 of 4 folders), 1990 October (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
    - George Sexton Associates. [Luman Reed Lighting], 1990 October-1991 January (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
    - 2nd Floor Lighting [George Sexton Associates], 1990 June-July (Offsite-box 4, Folder 7)
    - 2nd Floor North Renovation. General (1 of 2), 1990 July-September (Offsite-box 4, Folder 8)
      3 oversize blueline plans were moved to the following folder.
    - 2nd Floor North Renovation. General (2 of 2). Oversize, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 12)
      Includes three oversize bluelines: two of the 2nd Floor existing plan, one with the lighting plan by George Sexton Associates, and one of the proposed plan for the 2nd Floor North Gallery, also with the lighting plan.
    - 2nd Floor North Renovation. Asbestos Removal [Ambient Labs], 1989 November-1990 July (Offsite-box 4, Folder 9)
    - 2nd Floor North Gallery. Record of Expenses, 1990 July-November (Offsite-box 4, Folder 10)
    - 2nd Floor. Library Doors, 1990 May-June (Offsite-box 4, Folder 11)
    - 2nd Floor Renovations (1 of 2), 1991 February (Offsite-box 4, Folder 12)
      An oversize blueline plan was moved to the following folder.
    - 2nd Floor Renovations (2 of 2). Oversize, 1990 June (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 13)
      Includes a blueline of the 2nd Floor existing plan by Allan Greenberg, Architect, with the lighting plan by George Sexton Associates.
    - Severud Associates, 1989 July-1990 December, 1993 March (Offsite-box 4, Folder 13)
    - Print Room Renovation. Severud Associates (Structural Engineers), 1990 July-October (Offsite-box 4, Folder 14)
    - Print Room Renovation. Ambrosino, DePinto & Schmieder (Consulting Engineers), 1990 July-1991 February (Offsite-box 4, Folder 15)
    - 3rd Floor Hall. Collections Hall East, 1989 July (Offsite-box 4, Folder 16)
    - 3rd Floor. Office Renovations, 1989 August-1990 October (Offsite-box 4, Folder 17)
    - Renovations Contracts. Jewish Museum, 1990 July (Offsite-box 4, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Museum Reimbursables (2 folders), 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Renovations Permits (1 of 2 folders), 1989 October-1991 April (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
      Oversize plans were moved to the following folder.
    - Renovations Permits (2 of 2 folders). Oversize, 1990-1991 (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 14)
      Includes a blueline plan by Facade Maintenance Design for masonry repairs (sheet #A-1), as of March 8, 1991, and stamped by Department of Buildings on April 12, 1991. Includes two blueline plans by Facade Maintenance Design: 76th Street wall elevations and details (drawings #A1 and A2); stamped by the Department of Buildings on June 18, 1990.
    - 4th Floor. Asbestos Abatement Considerations and Specifications for Removal [Ambient Labs] (3 folders), 1990 January-September (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4-6)
    - Basement Clean-Up, 1989 May-December (Offsite-box 5, Folder 7)
    - Basement Decoration, 1990 November-December (Offsite-box 5, Folder 8)
    - Basement Renovations, 1990 May-December (Offsite-box 5, Folder 9)
    - Society Store Renovations, 1990 February-1991 April (Offsite-box 5, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Proposals & Estimates, 1989 May-August (Offsite-box 5, Folder 11)
    - Real Estate [Clippings], 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 12)
    - Shade Systems, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 13)
      Includes samples of SOL-R-VEIL brand fabric for window shading.
    - Architects (4 folders), 1990 November-1992 January (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1-4)
      Includes introductory and marketing material from various architectural and construction firms, including F&V/DeMilo; Hanscomb Associates Inc.; Nicholson & Galloway, Inc.; Kapell and Kostow; Butler Rogers Baskett; Einhorn Yaffee Prescott; William A. Hall Partnership; and Kracauer Froom Weintraub and Cameron.
    - Unsolicited Architecture Materials, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
      Includes marketing brochure from May Whitelaw Pinska and Kupiec Koutsomitis.
    - Richard Jansen, Architects, 1990 September-1991 January (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
    - Richard Jansen, Architects, 1990 April-November, 1992 April (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
    - BKD [Barbara Knowles Debs]. Richard Jansen, Architects. Projects (1 of 2), 1990 November-December (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
      Twelve oversize blueline plans were moved to the following folder.
    - BKD [Barbara Knowles Debs]. Richard Jansen, Architects. Projects (2 of 2). Oversize, 1990-1991 (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 15)
      Includes 12 blueline plans for a temporary admissions and information desk, a proposed ladder and stair to the auditorium control loft, proposed lobby lay-outs, and a proposed library lay-out.
    - 1st Floor South. Lighting., 1991 October (Offsite-box 6, Folder 9)
    - Library Stacks, 1991 July (Offsite-box 6, Folder 10)
    - Citibank Building Study, 1991 October-December (Offsite-box 6, Folder 11)
      Includes reports by engineers concerning the condition of 170 Central Park West and of 15 West 76th Street.
    - Building Reports (1 of 2), 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 12)
      One oversize blueline plan was moved to the following folder.
    - Building Reports (2 of 2). Oversize, 1989 September 22 (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 16)
      Includes two blueline drawings (#1) by H.B. Fishman & Co. of a roof plan (progress print).
    - [Project Administration], 1990 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 13)
      Includes minutes of construction meeting #4 of June 14, 1990, and a project schedule for May-September, likely 1990.
    - 4th Floor South & East Renovations, 1992 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 14)
    - N-YHS Building Schematics, 1992 April 16 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
      Includes plans of "existing conditions" by floor and schematics, by an unidentified drafter.
    - Floor Plans, 1991-1992? (Offsite-box 6, Folder 15)
    - [Floor Plans to Clayton-Wilson Associates], circa 1992 (Offsite-box 28, Folder circa 1992)
    - Telephone for Building, 1992 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 16)
      Includes a proposal from MCI Telecommunications Corporation for an outbound phone service plan named MCI Vision.
    - Emergency Roof Repairs, 1992 November-December (Offsite-box 6, Folder 17)
    - Capital Project. Miscellaneous, 1993 June-September (Offsite-box 6, Folder 18)
    - Capital Project. Cost Estimates, 1993? (Offsite-box 6, Folder 19)
    - Engineering Services Proposal. Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder., 1993 July (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
      Includes, as an enclosure to the 1993 proposal, a copy of the firm's December 1989 proposal for the "Master Plan" work specified at that time.
    - Engineering Services Proposal. Cosentini Associates, 1993 July (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2)
    - Engineering Services Proposal. Landmark Facilities Group, 1993 July (Offsite-box 7, Folder 3)
    - Feasibility Report, 1993 September 13 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
      Two copies of report prepared by Beyer Blinder Belle (architects), Ambrosino DePinto Schmieder (mechanical engineers), and Lehrer McGovern Bovis (construction managers).
    - Capital Improvement Plan. Meeting Agenda, 1994 July 13 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
    - 4th Floor Study Storage Area, 1994 December (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
    - Additional Files, circa 1984-1994 (Box -, Folder -)
      Following are additional files that relate to the above, but were found subsequent to processing and so were simply appended here.
    - [Allan Greenberg] Roof/Facade, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
      Includes documents prepared for the architects by Facade Maintenance Design (some of which are likely duplicates of documents found in the above folders), including a deficiency report (May 30, 1989), facade rehabilitation proposal (July 7, 1989), additional survey report (September 26, 1989), presentation to the Board of Trustees (December 13, 1989), and other documents.
    - [Allan Greenberg] Roof/Facade. Bid Specifications, 1990 September 20 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Allan Greenberg. Current Issues, 1993 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
      Includes the original, signed agreement with Greenberg concerning N-YHS's use of his firm's drawings after they were no longer involved with the renovation project.
    - Ambient Labs [Asbestos Reports] (4 folders), 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4-7)
    - Ambient Lab Proposal & Contract, 1994 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder (3 folders), 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9-11)
      Includes drafts and final of Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder's "Master Plan" of December 12, 1989, for the mechanical, electrical, plumbing, and life safety systems.
    - Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder (2 folders), 1989-1990, 1993 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - Art Preservation Systems. Environmental Conditions, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
    - Auditorium, 1992 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
      Includes documents from Richard Jansen (architect), Eldon Elder Associates (lighting), and the Electric Connection, Inc. See the folder for Richard Jansen in Subseries II.C. Architectural Plans for his drawings related to the auditorium and other projects.
    - Beyer Blinder Belle, 1993 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 5)
    - Capital Projects, 1990 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 6)
    - Capital Projects. Architects & Mechanical Engineers. Questionnaires & Interview, 1993 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 7)
    - Capital Project 1994. Preliminary Budget Estimates (Offsite-box 24, Folder 8)
    - [Capital Project] Pass-Through Contract. State of New York, 1993 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 9)
    - Capital Project. Current City $5 Mil, 1994 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 10)
    - Clayton-Wilson, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 11)
    - Dick Jansen. First Floor Lobby Renovations, 1990 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 12)
    - Floor Plans and Square Footage (3 folders), circa 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 13-15)
    - History of the N-YHS Building, circa 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 16)
      Includes documents related to the building's landmark status and the process for making various alterations.
    - Landmark Application (3 folders), 1990 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 17-19)
      Includes the application materials to the Landmarks Preservation Commission for repairing the damaged garden wall. The files include color photographs of the wall facing West 76th Street.
    - Lehrer McGovern Bovis (8 folders), 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1-8)
    - Lighting. 76th Street, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 9)
    - Lighting Systems Report (M. Prudhom), 1991 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 10)
    - Lighting. Survey of Power Requirements (George Sexton), 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 11)
    - Master Planning, 1989 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 12)
    - Morse Diesel Report, 1988 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 13)
    - Remco Maintenance Corp., 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 14)
    - Staff Space Needs, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 15)
    - Townhouse (2 folders), 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 16-17)
  - Subseries II.B. Construction Phases I-III, 1990-2001; 7.35 Linear feet
    The subseries includes documents that appear to be the files of Chief Operating Officer Ed Norris as they related to the implementation of construction work in three phases over the course of the late 1990s. Phase I involved installing a new roof, waterproofing the facade, upgrading the HVAC system, and overhauling the electrical system. Phase 2 included new modular chilling units and various interior renovations, such as lighting, smoke detection, handicap accessible toilet, altering certain rooms on the 2nd floor, etc. The third phase saw the development of the Luce Center on the 4th floor.
    The subseries includes extensive correspondence with N-YHS's architect for the project, Beyer Blinder Belle; the construction manager, Lehrer McGovern Bovis (also referred to by its later name, Bovis Lend Lease); and the New York City agencies funding the projects, the Department of Cultural Affairs and the Department of Design & Construction. The subseries also includes contracts, status reports and meeting notes, photographs (found in the monthly reports), and change orders. The series includes several of the periodic applications/requisitions from N-YHS for payment from New York City under the project's pass-through contract. These applications include the extensive support documentation of costs provided by Lehrer McGovern Bovis to N-YHS. Not all applications are in the files and in some instances only the requisition to N-YHS from Lehrer McGovern Bovis are in the files.
    The subseries includes the 1993 feasibility study underlying the project work and concept documents for what became the Luce Center. There are only a few architectural drawings for the work done in these phases.
    The bulk of the series is arranged in its original order: alphabetical by topic within the three project phases. After processing, a box of related files were found and added to the end of the container under the heading "Additional Files." These latter files were not labeled by project phase but generally appear to apply to Phase I and perhaps Phase II.
    Documents were re-housed to archival folders; the labels in the container list were transcribed from the original labels. Label titles modified in any substantive way by the processing archivist are those in [brackets].
    - Phase I: Ambient Labs, 1994 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
    - Phase I: Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder. Correspondence to:, 1999 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
    - Phase I: Ambrosino DePinto & Schmieder. Correspondence from:, 1994-1996 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
    - Phase I: Banner Plans, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
    - Phase I: Beyer Blinder Belle Contract, 1994 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
    - Phase I: Beyer Blinder Belle. Correspondence to:, 1994-1996 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
    - Phase I: Beyer Blinder Belle. Correspondence from:, 1994-1999 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
    - Phase I: Bidders List, 1994 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
    - Phase I: Bovis Lend Lease [Lehrer McGovern Bovis/LMB]. Correspondence to: (3 folders), 1994-1999 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 9-11)
    - Phase I: Bovis Lend Lease [Lehrer McGovern Bovis/LMB]. Correspondence from: (2 of 8 folders), 1994 January-June (Offsite-box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Phase I: Bovis Lend Lease [Lehrer McGovern Bovis/LMB]. Correspondence from: (6 of 8 folders), 1994 July-2000 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1-6)
    - Phase I: Capital Contracts, 1993-1997 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 7)
    - Phase I: Capital Issues, 1994 November-December (Offsite-box 9, Folder 8)
    - Phase I: Capital Items, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 9)
    - Phase I: Change Orders, 1994-2001 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 10)
      An additional file concerning change orders was found after processing. See below under the Additional Files section of the container list.
    - Phase I: Construction Contract (3 folders), 1993-1995 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - Phase I: Construction Meeting Minutes (2 folders), 1994-1997 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4-5)
    - Phase I: Department of Cultural Affairs. Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 6)
    - Phase I: Department of Design & Construction. Correspondence to:, 1996-2000 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 7)
    - Phase I: Department of Design & Construction. Correspondence from: (2 folders), 1995-2001 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Phase I: Department of General Services. Correspondence to:, 1994 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1)
    - Phase I: Department of General Services. Correspondence from: (2 folders), 1994-1998 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 2-3)
    - Phase I: Feasibility Study (2 folders), 1993 September 13 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4-5)
      Includes 4 copies of the study by Beyer Blinder Belle, Ambrosino DePinto Schmieder, and Lehrer McGovern Bovis, some lightly annotated.
    - Phase I: Greenberg, Architect, 1993 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 6)
    - Phase I: Handicap Ramp (1 of 2 folders), 1990, 1994-1997 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 7)
      An oversize set of blueline plans were moved to the following folder.
    - Phase I: Handicap Ramp (2 of 2 folders). Oversize, 1994 October (Drawer 12A-B7, Folder 17)
      Includes a set of blueline plans by architect Beyer Blinder Belle for a new ramp.
    - Phase I: Monthly Reports (3 folders), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 8-10)
      Additional monthly reports for 1996-1997 were found after processing. See below under the Additional Files section of the container list.
    - Phase I: PECO, Inc. Contract, 1994, 1996 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - Phase I: Permits/Landmark Commission, 1994-1999 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Phase I: Requisition for Payment No. 19 (2 folders), 2000 April (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3-4)
      Additional files of applications/requisitions for payments were found after processing. See below under the Additional Files section of the container list.
    - Phase I: Requisition for Payment No. 20, 2000 May (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - Phase I: Requisition for Payment No. 22, 2000 June (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - Phase I: Supplementary Report. Roof Restoration, 1989 September 22 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
      Includes roof consultant H.B. Fishman & Co., Inc's report, which includes color photographs of the roof and details.
    - Phase I: Trade Contracts (7 folders), 1994-1997 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2-8)
    - Phase II: Ambrosino DePinto Schmieder, 1996-1998, 2001 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    - Phase II: Beyer Blinder Belle, 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    - Phase II: Bovis Lend Lease [Lehrer McGovern Bovis]. Correspondence to: (2 folders), 1994, 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Phase II: Bovis Lend Lease [Lehrer McGovern Bovis]. Correspondence from: (3 folders), 1994-2001 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5-7)